text,start,end,entities,duration,top_three_entities
Elon Musk his fourth time on this The,2.04,8.52,"[('Elon Musk', 0, 9, 'PERSON'), ('fourth', 14, 20, 'ORDINAL')]",6.4799999999999995,"['Elon Musk', 'fourth']"
Lex Friedman about the Roman Empire as one Roman Empire at least once a day and half the population is confused whether world today and as you know uh war and uh Roman society and culture and it I like the Austra Hungarian Empire where ability to control our um limpic chimpanzee and in fact if if one looks at say chimpanzee Society it is not friendly I mean the bonovas are an exception um but chimpanzee Society,5.44,193.28,"[('Lex Friedman', 0, 12, 'PERSON'), ('the Roman Empire', 6, 22, 'GPE'), ('one', 26, 29, 'CARDINAL'), ('Roman Empire', 0, 12, 'GPE'), ('half', 0, 4, 'CARDINAL'), ('today', 6, 11, 'DATE'), ('Roman', 3, 8, 'NORP'), ('Austra', 9, 15, 'GPE'), ('Hungarian', 16, 25, 'NORP'), ('limpic', 26, 32, 'GPE'), ('one', 29, 32, 'CARDINAL'), ('Society', 18, 25, 'ORG'), ('bonovas', 20, 27, 'PRODUCT'), ('Society', 28, 35, 'ORG')]",187.84,"['one', 'Society', 'Lex Friedman']"
Romans said just War there's no just war,205.12,210.72,"[('Romans', 0, 6, 'NORP')]",5.599999999999994,['Romans']
yeah chimpan Society is a Like A too many Disney movies decides to raise or Che their fingers off and that kind people it's un unfortunate like that's I going on today and to see what the path current war in Israel and Gaza comes to Middle East um in Israel especially so uh the the goal of Hamas was to provoke an overreaction from Israel um they aggressive response possible from Israel response to um rally Muslims worldwide uh for the course of uh Gaza and Palestine which they have succeeded in Israel engage in the most cons for Israel to find the Hamas members and you know somehow because hos will then their um but Ian you really have if if you're Israel so really the question is like Gaza if you you've made at least a few uh Hamas members who will die Israeli that's the situation so but but I mean this is one of the and scale of War but to to imagine that War the first book starts off with a,213.2,605.6,"[('yeah chimpan Society', 0, 20, 'ORG'), ('Disney', 9, 15, 'ORG'), ('Che', 3, 6, 'PERSON'), ('un', 12, 14, 'ORG'), ('today', 9, 14, 'DATE'), ('Israel', 15, 21, 'GPE'), ('Gaza', 26, 30, 'GPE'), ('Middle East', 0, 11, 'LOC'), ('Israel', 18, 24, 'GPE'), ('Hamas', 19, 24, 'ORG'), ('Israel', 21, 27, 'GPE'), ('Israel', 34, 40, 'GPE'), ('Muslims', 21, 28, 'NORP'), ('Gaza', 24, 28, 'GPE'), ('Palestine', 0, 9, 'GPE'), ('Israel', 0, 6, 'GPE'), ('Israel', 4, 10, 'GPE'), ('Hamas', 12, 17, 'ORG'), ('hos', 16, 19, 'ORG'), ('Ian', 7, 10, 'PERSON'), ('Israel', 0, 6, 'GPE'), ('Gaza', 0, 4, 'GPE'), ('Hamas', 3, 8, 'ORG'), ('Israeli', 0, 7, 'NORP'), ('one', 26, 29, 'CARDINAL'), ('War', 13, 16, 'EVENT'), ('first', 8, 13, 'ORDINAL')]",392.40000000000003,"['Israel', 'Gaza', 'Hamas']"
gigantic Galactic War where trillions we are able to one day expand to you know full the Galaxy or whatever there the scale I mean the scale of War has it be stopped one of the things that few people people alive today who horrors of War at least in the US I mean lines in Ukraine and Russia who was in World War II uh he was severely in for almost six years in the in East North Africa and Italy uh all his finish High School um he had to drop out,602.519,707.68,"[('Galactic War', 9, 21, 'EVENT'), ('one day', 15, 22, 'DATE'), ('Galaxy', 14, 20, 'PRODUCT'), ('War', 30, 33, 'EVENT'), ('one', 14, 17, 'CARDINAL'), ('today', 24, 29, 'DATE'), ('US', 31, 33, 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 9, 16, 'GPE'), ('Russia', 21, 27, 'GPE'), ('World War II', 7, 19, 'EVENT'), ('almost six years', 7, 23, 'DATE'), ('East', 34, 38, 'LOC'), ('North Africa', 0, 12, 'GPE'), ('Italy', 17, 22, 'GPE'), ('High School', 7, 18, 'ORG')]",105.16099999999994,"['Galactic War', 'one day', 'Galaxy']"
British intelligence in London that's died you know 20 years ago or longer,728.6,769.6800000000001,"[('British', 0, 7, 'NORP'), ('London', 24, 30, 'GPE'), ('20 years ago', 14, 26, 'DATE')]",41.08000000000004,"['British', 'London', '20 years ago']"
actually 30 years ago remember World War II not many and the bombs pointed at United States to make times there's two major Wars going on potential obviously Global Theron how do you hope the war in Ukraine comes and uh infantry trenches it's World War One all over again sort of Cru or or peace a year ago was flower of Ukrainian and Russian Youth the Russian boys as well as the Ukrainian boys because they Russian boys World War I it's like young boys who that so Vladimir zalinski said that he's interested in talking to Putin directly Ukrainian youth to be to die uh in trenches uh whether he talks to Putin or possibility of war between us and China question of Taiwan and one China policy where these two superpowers opposed to what one side or another the whole thing yeah so that Athens and Sparta it's classic case the thing about the Greeks is they really wrote down a the Greeks they really wrote a know what led up to the pelian war between um the spoton and Athenian coming I mean the Spartans didn't right they also weren't very foros by their the the Athenians and the other Greeks leader of of Greece um but but Athens be a clash between Athens and Sparta uh well how do we avoid that and if if one uh group one civilization or or country or know the United States has been the think around 1890 from an economic standpoint so the United States has been likely to be two perhaps three times larger than that of the US so imagine,767.079,1368.039,"[('30 years ago', 9, 21, 'DATE'), ('World War II', 9, 21, 'EVENT'), ('United States', 17, 30, 'GPE'), ('two', 14, 17, 'CARDINAL'), ('Global Theron', 20, 33, 'ORG'), ('Ukraine', 27, 34, 'GPE'), ('World War', 30, 39, 'EVENT'), ('One', 0, 3, 'CARDINAL'), ('Cru', 8, 11, 'ORG'), ('a year ago', 24, 34, 'DATE'), ('Ukrainian', 10, 19, 'NORP'), ('Russian', 24, 31, 'NORP'), ('Russian', 4, 11, 'NORP'), ('Ukrainian', 0, 9, 'NORP'), ('Russian', 28, 35, 'NORP'), ('World War I', 0, 11, 'EVENT'), ('Vladimir zalinski', 8, 25, 'PERSON'), ('Putin', 25, 30, 'PERSON'), ('Ukrainian', 0, 9, 'NORP'), ('Putin', 32, 37, 'PERSON'), ('China', 34, 39, 'GPE'), ('Taiwan', 12, 18, 'GPE'), ('one', 23, 26, 'CARDINAL'), ('China', 27, 32, 'GPE'), ('two', 12, 15, 'CARDINAL'), ('one', 16, 19, 'CARDINAL'), ('Athens', 29, 35, 'GPE'), ('Sparta', 0, 6, 'GPE'), ('Greeks', 4, 10, 'NORP'), ('Greeks', 4, 10, 'NORP'), ('the pelian war', 20, 34, 'EVENT'), ('Athenian', 26, 34, 'NORP'), ('Spartans', 18, 26, 'NORP'), ('foros', 23, 28, 'NORP'), ('Athenians', 8, 17, 'NORP'), ('Greeks', 32, 38, 'NORP'), ('Greece', 13, 19, 'GPE'), ('Athens', 31, 37, 'GPE'), ('Athens', 19, 25, 'GPE'), ('Sparta', 0, 6, 'NORP'), ('one', 6, 9, 'CARDINAL'), ('one', 6, 9, 'CARDINAL'), ('the United States', 5, 22, 'GPE'), ('1890', 13, 17, 'DATE'), ('the United States', 14, 31, 'GPE'), ('two', 13, 16, 'CARDINAL'), ('three', 25, 30, 'CARDINAL'), ('US', 24, 26, 'GPE')]",600.96,"['one', 'two', 'Ukrainian']"
Gap in understanding of each other and you are an American obviously you've the United States but you also work with China I've spent a lot of time in China some things about China that people Chinese well uh the the sheer number of really smart hardworking people in China people are there in China there's far so I mean the architecture in China that's in recent years is far more impressive than the US I mean the the we have in the US I I mean I recommend somebody just go to Shanghai and Beijing look at the buildings and go to you take the train from Beijing to Shion you have the Terra Cotta Warriors um China's got incredible history very long standpoint um sort of one of one of the written language and and then China so um now China um historically has,1387.72,1497.919,"[('Gap', 0, 3, 'ORG'), ('American', 11, 19, 'NORP'), ('the United States', 0, 17, 'GPE'), ('China', 0, 5, 'GPE'), ('China', 34, 39, 'GPE'), ('China', 18, 23, 'GPE'), ('Chinese', 0, 7, 'NORP'), ('China', 35, 40, 'GPE'), ('China', 20, 25, 'GPE'), ('China', 30, 35, 'GPE'), ('recent years', 10, 22, 'DATE'), ('US', 20, 22, 'GPE'), ('US', 15, 17, 'GPE'), ('Shanghai', 20, 28, 'GPE'), ('Beijing', 0, 7, 'GPE'), ('Beijing', 24, 31, 'GPE'), ('the Terra Cotta Warriors', 9, 33, 'ORG'), ('China', 0, 5, 'GPE'), ('one', 22, 25, 'CARDINAL'), ('one', 29, 32, 'CARDINAL'), ('China', 30, 35, 'GPE'), ('China', 10, 15, 'GPE')]",110.19900000000007,"['China', 'US', 'Beijing']"
um in the Three Kingdoms War I believe,1507.12,1512.9189999999999,"[('the Three Kingdoms War', 6, 28, 'EVENT')]",5.798999999999978,['the Three Kingdoms War']
they lost about 70% of their brutal internal Wars like civil wars that make the US Civil War that China is not China is a sort of one entity of one people who understand China would agree that people in China think about China 10 times more than they think about anything outside of China so it's like 90% of their consideration is uh you the good news the history of China suggests that China is not inquisitive been inquisitive um the US is one of the also one of the rare cases that has not been inquisitive like after World War II the us could have basically taken over and the United States could have taken um the United States actually helped Europe you it helped rebuild Japan um this is very unusual behavior um you know the US did conspicuous acts always like well America's done bad things well of course America's done bad generally you know one one sort of test War MH or let's um you know no offense to the Russians but let's say you're in Germany it's 1945 you got the Russian army coming on one side you got the French British and American armies coming to the other side perfect but I recommend um being a PW with the Americans that would be my so and in fact Von Brown um yeah took to be captured by the Americans Y and uh in fact the SS was under orders to execute bar Brown and all of the uh German rocket Engineers uh and they woods they left in the middle of winter then just cycled West as fast as he could and found found a US Patrol um so anyway that's that's one that's one way PW it's not fun anywhere but some places so um anyway so so so like America has generally a benevolent Force um and uh half right knows that so so I think there are in this way China and uh the,1509.64,1778.1200000000001,"[('about 70%', 10, 19, 'PERCENT'), ('brutal internal', 0, 15, 'ORG'), ('the US Civil War', 10, 26, 'EVENT'), ('China', 5, 10, 'GPE'), ('China', 0, 5, 'GPE'), ('one', 19, 22, 'CARDINAL'), ('one', 33, 36, 'CARDINAL'), ('China', 22, 27, 'GPE'), ('China', 15, 20, 'GPE'), ('China', 33, 38, 'GPE'), ('10', 0, 2, 'CARDINAL'), ('China', 20, 25, 'GPE'), ('90%', 0, 3, 'PERCENT'), ('China', 29, 34, 'GPE'), ('China', 14, 19, 'GPE'), ('US', 24, 26, 'GPE'), ('one', 5, 8, 'CARDINAL'), ('World War II', 28, 40, 'EVENT'), ('us', 4, 6, 'GPE'), ('the United States', 4, 21, 'GPE'), ('the United States', 3, 20, 'GPE'), ('Europe', 0, 6, 'LOC'), ('Japan', 0, 5, 'GPE'), ('US', 16, 18, 'GPE'), ('America', 17, 24, 'GPE'), ('America', 22, 29, 'GPE'), ('one', 19, 22, 'CARDINAL'), ('War MH', 0, 6, 'ORG'), ('Russians', 30, 38, 'NORP'), ('Germany', 24, 31, 'GPE'), ('1945', 0, 4, 'DATE'), ('Russian', 17, 24, 'NORP'), ('one', 0, 3, 'CARDINAL'), ('French', 21, 27, 'NORP'), ('British', 28, 35, 'NORP'), ('American', 0, 8, 'NORP'), ('PW', 35, 37, 'GPE'), ('Americans', 9, 18, 'NORP'), ('Von Brown', 15, 24, 'PERSON'), ('Americans', 22, 31, 'NORP'), ('SS', 21, 23, 'ORG'), ('Brown', 15, 20, 'PERSON'), ('German', 3, 9, 'NORP'), ('the middle of winter', 19, 39, 'DATE'), ('West', 17, 21, 'LOC'), ('US', 24, 26, 'GPE'), ('one', 32, 35, 'CARDINAL'), ('PW', 0, 2, 'GPE'), ('America', 27, 34, 'GPE'), ('Force', 23, 28, 'ORG'), ('half', 0, 4, 'CARDINAL'), ('China', 22, 27, 'GPE')]",268.48,"['China', 'one', 'US']"
United States are similar NE neither principle I guess um now now China does Taiwan they've been very clear about not there like like Hawaii or something Hawaii you know um and Hawaii is pretty significant for China the island of fosa not not Taiwan that is um not part of China but should is because of the US Pacific yes China has been very clear that um,1776.279,1854.279,"[('United States', 0, 13, 'GPE'), ('NE', 26, 28, 'LOC'), ('China', 29, 34, 'GPE'), ('Taiwan', 0, 6, 'GPE'), ('Hawaii', 20, 26, 'GPE'), ('Hawaii', 0, 6, 'GPE'), ('Hawaii', 7, 13, 'GPE'), ('China', 0, 5, 'GPE'), ('Taiwan', 33, 39, 'GPE'), ('China', 23, 28, 'GPE'), ('the US Pacific', 14, 28, 'LOC'), ('China', 4, 9, 'GPE')]",78.0,"['China', 'Hawaii', 'Taiwan']"
they will incorporate Taiwan uh,1851.2,1857.919,"[('Taiwan', 22, 28, 'GPE')]",6.719000000000051,['Taiwan']
their standpoint is 100% absolutely so in after World War I the on Germany um and um and and you know settled JY with uh was a lot of BL there was a fair quite a bit of blame to um go around for World put it all in Germany seeds for World War want Vengeance um so after World War II they're like well the Treaty of asai was a huge mistake um in World War I R Revolt Germany we're going to help reor you know Austria and the other you know Italy and whatnot uh it's amazing on many levels first of one I wish first of all I wish I um our our AI Gro is modeled after the Hedgehog got to the Galaxy uh which is one of my favorite books uh which is like this AI system has an what it's all about the Curiosity you MH um so for the other sort of AIS out hallucinates Mo most when you least um Trace things back to physics first basically well as you said I think one,1860.48,2285.2000000000003,"[('100%', 20, 24, 'PERCENT'), ('World War I the', 23, 38, 'EVENT'), ('Germany', 3, 10, 'GPE'), ('JY', 25, 27, 'PERSON'), ('BL', 13, 15, 'ORG'), ('World', 33, 38, 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('Germany', 14, 21, 'GPE'), ('World War', 10, 19, 'EVENT'), ('World War II', 27, 39, 'EVENT'), ('Treaty', 22, 28, 'LAW'), ('World War', 21, 30, 'EVENT'), ('Revolt Germany', 2, 16, 'GPE'), ('Austria', 14, 21, 'GPE'), ('Italy', 5, 10, 'GPE'), ('first', 31, 36, 'ORDINAL'), ('first', 11, 16, 'ORDINAL'), ('AI Gro', 13, 19, 'PRODUCT'), ('Galaxy', 20, 26, 'PRODUCT'), ('one', 0, 3, 'CARDINAL'), ('AI', 10, 12, 'PRODUCT'), ('Curiosity', 24, 33, 'ORG'), ('AIS', 31, 34, 'ORG'), ('Mo', 13, 15, 'PERSON'), ('first', 32, 37, 'ORDINAL'), ('one', 35, 38, 'CARDINAL')]",424.72000000000025,"['first', 'Germany', 'World War']"
of the big goals of XI is to understand,2283.24,2288.9199999999996,"[('XI', 20, 22, 'CARDINAL')]",5.679999999999836,['XI']
three-word uh,2288.92,2295.119,"[('three', 0, 5, 'CARDINAL')]",6.199000000000069,['three']
"coming up with The Theory of Everything physics discoveries if an AI cannot not equal to humans let Al nor has MH now the the range of possibilities together to get an AI system a large it doesn't make any sense MH so it has bunch of first and then you get no ey in Team America oh wait there whole Consciousness emotion atoms and maybe AI can pave the path to the Discovery what whatever the hell conscious um one of the two I like the beginning of the universe the first time aliens that's one of the like the FY of Earth for believe the archaeological record Earth is about 4 and half billion the first writing is only about 5,000 there to the ancient samarians who",2310.599,2776.3590000000004,"[('The Theory of Everything', 15, 39, 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('AI', 26, 28, 'PRODUCT'), ('Al', 24, 26, 'PERSON'), ('MH', 0, 2, 'ORG'), ('AI', 19, 21, 'PRODUCT'), ('MH', 26, 28, 'ORG'), ('first', 9, 14, 'ORDINAL'), ('Team America', 9, 21, 'LOC'), ('Consciousness', 6, 19, 'PRODUCT'), ('AI', 16, 18, 'PRODUCT'), ('Discovery', 4, 13, 'PRODUCT'), ('one', 13, 16, 'CARDINAL'), ('two', 24, 27, 'CARDINAL'), ('first', 30, 35, 'ORDINAL'), ('one', 14, 17, 'CARDINAL'), ('Earth', 3, 8, 'LOC'), ('Earth', 7, 12, 'LOC'), ('first', 4, 9, 'ORDINAL'), ('only about 5,000', 21, 37, 'CARDINAL'), ('samarians', 21, 30, 'NORP')]",465.7600000000002,"['AI', 'first', 'MH']"
"archaic pre uniform was the first actual 5,000 years started that's 1 millionth of Earth's",2776.359,2793.7599999999998,"[('first', 28, 33, 'ORDINAL'), ('5,000 years', 0, 11, 'DATE'), ('1 millionth', 15, 26, 'CARDINAL'), ('Earth', 30, 35, 'LOC')]",17.40099999999984,"['first', '5,000 years', '1 millionth']"
4 and half billion will heat heat the Earth up it's some and and Earth will become like Venus annihilation of all life on Earth is a scale uh half a billion standards but that's only 10% longer than Earth has been around at all mhm so if if life had taken 10% longer to evolve on Earth it wouldn't exist at Earth developed a lot of cool stuff very bunch of long Dead one planet civilizations don't pass through and one the Amazon the on contact tribes were Andre kathi said it's like the ants in,2812.92,3009.44,"[('4 and half billion', 0, 18, 'MONEY'), ('Earth', 19, 24, 'LOC'), ('Earth', 8, 13, 'LOC'), ('Venus', 31, 36, 'LOC'), ('Earth', 28, 33, 'LOC'), ('scale uh half a billion', 0, 23, 'CARDINAL'), ('only 10%', 21, 29, 'PERCENT'), ('Earth', 5, 10, 'LOC'), ('10%', 21, 24, 'PERCENT'), ('Earth', 10, 15, 'LOC'), ('Earth', 0, 5, 'LOC'), ('one', 19, 22, 'CARDINAL'), ('one', 37, 40, 'CARDINAL'), ('Amazon', 4, 10, 'ORG'), ('Andre kathi', 0, 11, 'PERSON')]",196.51999999999998,"['Earth', 'one', '4 and half billion']"
the Amazon asking where's,3006.72,3011.3999999999996,"[('Amazon', 4, 10, 'ORG')]",4.679999999999836,['Amazon']
between VAR that wner hog talking about the jungle no I have not but wner hog has a,3019.48,3038.359,"[('VAR', 8, 11, 'ORG'), ('wner hog', 5, 13, 'ORG'), ('wner hog', 18, 26, 'PERSON')]",18.878999999999905,"['wner hog', 'VAR']"
yeah it's on YouTube it's it's,3041.119,3047.799,"[('YouTube', 13, 20, 'PRODUCT')]",6.679999999999836,['YouTube']
bear documentary The Bear documentary like 70 miles away penguin has just head you know this is the first time in the history of Earth that it's been possible for life to extend beyond Earth um that want to be one of those lame One Planet would be one planet there's not going to be a Wikipedia entry for one of those and uh pause uh do SpaceX have an you're with Einstein that you believe in Spinosa yes uh so you know that's a view physics or as Einstein said through the lawful Harmony of the world yeah I would Tesla we create simulations all the time back super high Heating and um overal do so maybe uh we both play Diablo maybe Diablo was created to see if a druid your character could defeat Uber Lilith hatred uh in the Eternal realm yeah yeah 100 nightmare Dungeons and still I I I can cruise through tier 100 nightmare the second hottest boss is durial durial games um at one point I was you know was the first paid orts tournament in the US um we doing four person Quake um we came second I was the second best would have come first except the best second but I got money for it and no spring spring chicken these days and um the to be totally Frank it's driving me crazy trying to beat Lilith as a druid basically try trying to beat,3051.44,3459.599,"[('Bear', 21, 25, 'ORG'), ('70 miles', 5, 13, 'QUANTITY'), ('first', 21, 26, 'ORDINAL'), ('Earth', 11, 16, 'LOC'), ('Earth', 26, 31, 'LOC'), ('One', 29, 32, 'CARDINAL'), ('one', 9, 12, 'CARDINAL'), ('one', 25, 28, 'CARDINAL'), ('SpaceX', 25, 31, 'PERSON'), ('Einstein', 12, 20, 'PERSON'), ('Spinosa', 0, 7, 'PERSON'), ('Einstein', 14, 22, 'PERSON'), ('Harmony', 7, 14, 'PRODUCT'), ('Tesla', 0, 5, 'ORG'), ('Heating', 16, 23, 'ORG'), ('Diablo', 28, 34, 'ORG'), ('Diablo', 0, 6, 'ORG'), ('Lilith', 33, 39, 'PERSON'), ('Eternal', 17, 24, 'ORG'), ('100', 0, 3, 'CARDINAL'), ('Dungeons', 14, 22, 'ORG'), ('100', 24, 27, 'CARDINAL'), ('second', 4, 10, 'ORDINAL'), ('durial durial', 27, 40, 'PERSON'), ('one', 12, 15, 'CARDINAL'), ('first', 8, 13, 'ORDINAL'), ('US', 4, 6, 'GPE'), ('four', 19, 23, 'CARDINAL'), ('second', 11, 17, 'ORDINAL'), ('second', 28, 34, 'ORDINAL'), ('first', 16, 21, 'ORDINAL'), ('second', 0, 6, 'ORDINAL'), ('these days', 25, 35, 'DATE'), ('Frank', 21, 26, 'PERSON'), ('Lilith', 24, 30, 'PERSON'), ('druid', 0, 5, 'ORG')]",408.1590000000001,"['second', 'first', 'one']"
player yeah and I think Diablo so you're with the Paragon board and the build are trying to figure out the Paragon board the SS have huge balls in um the say SS have huge balls um they do uh lth with a because you get these seasonally but to defeat hatred imposs it's impossible it seems like like the idea that Elon Musk because I saw I was playing diao yesterday and I,3476.2,3573.1600000000003,"[('Diablo', 24, 30, 'PERSON'), ('Paragon', 9, 16, 'ORG'), ('Paragon', 25, 32, 'ORG'), ('SS', 4, 6, 'ORG'), ('SS', 4, 6, 'ORG'), ('lth', 0, 3, 'ORG'), ('seasonally', 0, 10, 'DATE'), ('imposs', 0, 6, 'ORG'), ('Elon Musk', 19, 28, 'PERSON'), ('yesterday', 23, 32, 'DATE')]",96.96000000000049,"['Paragon', 'SS', 'Diablo']"
saw 100 level 100 Druid just run by I,3569.44,3575.68,"[('100', 4, 7, 'CARDINAL'), ('Druid', 18, 23, 'PRODUCT')]",6.239999999999782,"['100', 'Druid']"
Elon Musk is fighting goldilock zone um and I guess you best game ever top five for sure I think P Dynamic R TV even doesn't need to be a strategy you use to solve one battle is you said Druid on Eternal against Uber Lilith is the hardest boss battle you've four on I I'm not sure it's possible but maybe if I just tweak that Paragon board well that's the human Spirit right there one of those things where you wish for wish for World Peace sounds goodh but nature whether it's 1984 with surveillance and fear or Brave New World go to Brave New World we could ask it Som it's going to go to Brave New World around since the 1950s it's used to,3580.2,3937.16,"[('Elon Musk', 0, 9, 'PERSON'), ('goldilock zone', 0, 14, 'PERSON'), ('five', 19, 23, 'CARDINAL'), ('P Dynamic', 0, 9, 'PRODUCT'), ('one', 26, 29, 'CARDINAL'), ('Druid on Eternal', 9, 25, 'ORG'), ('Lilith', 0, 6, 'PERSON'), ('four', 0, 4, 'CARDINAL'), ('Paragon', 27, 34, 'ORG'), ('Spirit', 22, 28, 'PRODUCT'), ('one', 0, 3, 'CARDINAL'), ('World Peace', 9, 20, 'EVENT'), ('1984', 20, 24, 'DATE'), ('Brave New World', 25, 40, 'ORG'), ('Brave New World', 6, 21, 'LOC'), ('Brave New World', 24, 39, 'ORG'), ('the 1950s', 13, 22, 'DATE')]",356.96000000000004,"['Brave New World', 'one', 'Elon Musk']"
risks it's pretty good oh wait a minute healthcare professional and remember in first ah my apologies I was thinking of now this Huxley dystopia now Som is a altering hucog genic drug that's used to by the way Elon just read directly from Nails it in conclusion Som from Brave,3959.16,4125.679,"[('a minute', 31, 39, 'TIME'), ('healthcare professional', 0, 23, 'ORG'), ('first', 0, 5, 'ORDINAL'), ('Huxley', 9, 15, 'PERSON'), ('hucog', 9, 14, 'ORG'), ('Elon', 11, 15, 'ORG'), ('Som from Brave', 23, 37, 'ORG')]",166.51900000000023,"['a minute', 'healthcare professional', 'first']"
New World is fictional drug that used to,4123.88,4127.12,"[('New World', 0, 9, 'ORG')]",3.2399999999997817,['New World']
headon nailed know squashed uh dis in my C5 C6 so it efficiently is a big Focus for xai uh what's the uh first of all what's the with from first principles and think about things in the limit One Direction other so um in the limit even at the CF wat so that's where I I think probably standpoint of AI is that we have a shortage in about a year ironically have a silic and shortage today um a probably in about a year and then just about two years I I gave a speech for roughly 1/3 if very rough terms 1/3 electricity 1/3 transport 1/3 heating um second or the worst day of the year or,4139.52,4415.36,"[('headon', 0, 6, 'PERSON'), ('C5 C6', 27, 32, 'PRODUCT'), ('Focus for xai', 21, 34, 'ORG'), ('first', 17, 22, 'ORDINAL'), ('first', 10, 15, 'ORDINAL'), ('One', 26, 29, 'CARDINAL'), ('CF', 37, 39, 'PRODUCT'), ('wat', 0, 3, 'PERSON'), ('AI', 14, 16, 'ORG'), ('about a year', 12, 24, 'DATE'), ('today', 26, 31, 'DATE'), ('about a year', 12, 24, 'DATE'), ('about two years', 0, 15, 'DATE'), ('roughly 1/3', 0, 11, 'CARDINAL'), ('1/3', 32, 35, 'CARDINAL'), ('1/3', 12, 15, 'CARDINAL'), ('1/3', 26, 29, 'CARDINAL'), ('second', 0, 6, 'ORDINAL'), ('the worst day of the year', 10, 35, 'DATE')]",275.83999999999924,"['1/3', 'first', 'about a year']"
blackout for several days in in in,4417.48,4421.12,"[('several days', 13, 25, 'DATE')]",3.6400000000003274,['several days']
"Austin you've got a Hydro power plant you can can you can produce energy at night and use it during the day so you can for power plants is anywhere from 2 to 5 first principle of reasoning in this probably in about a year um three 300,000 volts and it's got to step about Google and Microsoft with open AI ensure with xai and uh Tesla AI work Cassandra on the subject for over a careful in how we develop AI objective third party who can be like a publicly um you know Jeff Hinton for example left Google and he voiced strong concerns but now he's not at Google",4419.36,4661.239,"[('Austin', 0, 6, 'PERSON'), ('Hydro', 13, 18, 'ORG'), ('night', 30, 35, 'TIME'), ('the day', 14, 21, 'DATE'), ('2', 34, 35, 'CARDINAL'), ('first', 0, 5, 'ORDINAL'), ('about a year', 12, 24, 'DATE'), ('three 300,000 volts', 0, 19, 'QUANTITY'), ('Google', 6, 12, 'ORG'), ('Microsoft', 17, 26, 'ORG'), ('Tesla', 23, 28, 'ORG'), ('AI', 29, 31, 'PRODUCT'), ('Cassandra', 0, 9, 'PERSON'), ('AI', 26, 28, 'PRODUCT'), ('third', 10, 15, 'ORDINAL'), ('Jeff Hinton', 21, 32, 'PERSON'), ('Google', 13, 19, 'ORG'), ('Google', 29, 35, 'ORG')]",241.8789999999999,"['Google', 'AI', 'Austin']"
I like I know Tesla gets a lot of 100 regulatory agencies Domestic Bally regulations that Tesla has to adhere to,4664.84,4681.08,"[('Tesla', 14, 19, 'ORG'), ('100', 0, 3, 'CARDINAL'), ('Domestic Bally', 24, 38, 'ORG'), ('Tesla', 17, 22, 'ORG')]",16.23999999999978,"['Tesla', '100', 'Domestic Bally']"
for SpaceX for Starship launch is Rocket and I'm like wait a second how a challenge at one point is that they shock MH and um now the ocean's very big zero and and and so then we will then we you do an NDA or essentially zero um then there's another until you know a few months ago uh that of the look at the look at the Pacific what percentage of the Pacific consists,4689.96,4827.879999999999,"[('SpaceX for Starship', 4, 23, 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('a second', 25, 33, 'TIME'), ('one', 15, 18, 'CARDINAL'), ('MH', 6, 8, 'ORG'), ('zero', 0, 4, 'CARDINAL'), ('NDA', 10, 13, 'ORG'), ('zero', 12, 16, 'CARDINAL'), ('a few months ago', 15, 31, 'DATE'), ('Pacific', 31, 38, 'LOC'), ('Pacific', 23, 30, 'LOC')]",137.91999999999916,"['zero', 'Pacific', 'SpaceX for Starship']"
whales like basically 0% um and if our that is the the Fate haded that's a well however it emerged yes well I mean one one of the things that's pretty wild is California we had to they were worried seals would be dismayed by the Sonic rockets launched out of vur and the seal play Sonic Boom sounds to it to see if,4831.12,4900.239,"[('0%', 22, 24, 'PERCENT'), ('Fate', 16, 20, 'PERSON'), ('one', 35, 38, 'CARDINAL'), ('one', 0, 3, 'CARDINAL'), ('California', 0, 10, 'GPE'), ('Sonic', 31, 36, 'ORG'), ('vur', 24, 27, 'ORG'), ('Sonic Boom', 5, 15, 'PERSON')]",69.11899999999969,"['one', '0%', 'Fate']"
pros and cons of open sourcing AI to you,4995.8,5000.320000000001,"[('AI', 31, 33, 'PRODUCT')]",4.520000000000437,['AI']
"8,000 A1 100s running at Peak um and Rock's going to get a lot better doubling our compute every couple months for the next several months there's a",5027.76,5044.28,"[('8,000', 0, 5, 'CARDINAL'), ('A1 100s', 6, 13, 'ORG'), ('Peak', 25, 29, 'LOC'), ('Rock', 7, 11, 'ORG'), ('every couple months', 21, 40, 'DATE'), ('the next several months', 4, 27, 'DATE')]",16.519999999999527,"['8,000', 'A1 100s', 'Peak']"
zero to grock one by itself just Gro Gro Gro state-ofthe-art GPT 35 and so I mean time delay you know I don't know six six months even Larry Page um back when he and I were Larry did not care about AI safety or at and at one point he called me a speciest Larry uh still on team robot to be and Google Google had acquired deep mind they had uh probably two-thirds of all AI researchers in the world MH they had charge you know Larry pagee did not care mind and maybe you and Larry Paige can to be friends with Larry again um he openingi um and moment was recruiting ilas s Sky um so I love Ilia he's so brilliant ilo's good battle um it was mostly Demis on one recruit Ilia and Ilia went back and forth you know kind of stay at Google he he he did agree to join open AI that was one of the toughest recruiting battles the the Lynch pin for opening I being Larry I haven't seen him in ages um and met I met Larry Page before he got funding for Google or actually I guess before he got Venture funding I think it he got the first like 100k from I think known each other that whole time just 20 years yeah since maybe 98 or something happened since then yeah 25 years A lot has happened insan but of code is very small MH so um how do you by the way Ser to,5044.28,5382.28,"[('zero', 0, 4, 'CARDINAL'), ('Gro Gro Gro', 12, 23, 'PRODUCT'), ('GPT', 16, 19, 'ORG'), ('six', 33, 36, 'CARDINAL'), ('months', 0, 6, 'DATE'), ('Larry Page', 0, 10, 'PERSON'), ('Larry', 0, 5, 'PERSON'), ('AI', 25, 27, 'PRODUCT'), ('one', 7, 10, 'CARDINAL'), ('Larry', 0, 5, 'PERSON'), ('Google Google', 0, 13, 'ORG'), ('two-thirds', 21, 31, 'CARDINAL'), ('AI', 0, 2, 'ORG'), ('MH', 28, 30, 'ORG'), ('Larry', 16, 21, 'PERSON'), ('Larry Paige', 23, 34, 'PERSON'), ('Larry', 19, 24, 'PERSON'), ('openingi um and', 0, 15, 'ORG'), ('ilas', 22, 26, 'PERSON'), ('Ilia', 5, 9, 'PERSON'), ('ilo', 28, 31, 'ORG'), ('Demis', 24, 29, 'GPE'), ('one', 33, 36, 'CARDINAL'), ('Ilia', 8, 12, 'PRODUCT'), ('Ilia', 17, 21, 'PERSON'), ('Google', 31, 37, 'ORG'), ('AI', 29, 31, 'ORG'), ('one', 0, 3, 'CARDINAL'), ('Lynch', 8, 13, 'PERSON'), ('Larry', 0, 5, 'PERSON'), ('Larry Page', 10, 20, 'PERSON'), ('Google', 12, 18, 'ORG'), ('Venture', 14, 21, 'ORG'), ('first', 11, 16, 'ORDINAL'), ('100k', 22, 26, 'CARDINAL'), ('20', 38, 40, 'CARDINAL'), ('98', 23, 25, 'CARDINAL'), ('25', 25, 27, 'CARDINAL'), ('insan', 25, 30, 'PERSON'), ('MH', 22, 24, 'ORG'), ('Ser', 28, 31, 'PRODUCT')]",338.0,"['Larry', 'AI', 'one']"
xplatform uh should be AI recommended and match the two MH explicitly follow someone that's one goes it first picks 1500 tweets from a pool of hundreds of millions first all hundreds of millions of posts every single day and it has to pick 1500 from rank those 1500 MH with some with some to go from several hundreds million to a handful is takes 220 seconds of CPU time where there's more than one degree of Prett good if if there's at least like hundred sort of vectors associated with posting like two three hour videos on like tweet for 2 hours come on tweet made sense when it was like 140 characters of text mm cuz it's like a bunch of TW like little birds tweeting Apple for example posted like the entire their number one social media thing ever posted an entire hourong episode of so neur that perspective it becomes really same pool as a three-hour video yeah I case of Apple posting like an entire that that hourong video um and you can having the AI actually watch the movie to like the movie MH convert the movie actually frankly the AI will be better you know it could be like a Coca-Cola ad on the EX system um and um McDonald's Sayes too and and uh you know so so they posted on the xplatform how hard is it certainly un regreted minutes it's a this drug called Reg me you just take one one pillar one one dose of regret I yeah there's a French song like that not regret yeah I regret nothing yeah Edith head I applaud the People's Republic of,5399.04,6005.4800000000005,"[('xplatform', 0, 9, 'PERSON'), ('AI', 23, 25, 'PRODUCT'), ('two', 14, 17, 'CARDINAL'), ('one', 33, 36, 'CARDINAL'), ('first', 8, 13, 'ORDINAL'), ('1500', 20, 24, 'CARDINAL'), ('hundreds of millions', 8, 28, 'CARDINAL'), ('first', 29, 34, 'ORDINAL'), ('hundreds of millions', 0, 20, 'CARDINAL'), ('single day', 0, 10, 'DATE'), ('1500', 30, 34, 'CARDINAL'), ('1500', 11, 15, 'CARDINAL'), ('several hundreds million', 11, 35, 'CARDINAL'), ('220 seconds', 17, 28, 'TIME'), ('more than one', 14, 27, 'CARDINAL'), ('Prett', 0, 5, 'PERSON'), ('hundred', 0, 7, 'CARDINAL'), ('two', 13, 16, 'CARDINAL'), ('three hour', 17, 27, 'TIME'), ('2 hours', 15, 22, 'TIME'), ('140', 28, 31, 'CARDINAL'), ('mm', 19, 21, 'PERSON'), ('TW', 9, 11, 'ORG'), ('Apple', 0, 5, 'ORG'), ('one', 13, 16, 'CARDINAL'), ('hourong', 17, 24, 'GPE'), ('neur', 0, 4, 'ORG'), ('three-hour', 15, 25, 'TIME'), ('Apple', 8, 13, 'ORG'), ('hourong', 10, 17, 'GPE'), ('AI', 11, 13, 'PRODUCT'), ('MH', 18, 20, 'ORG'), ('AI', 21, 23, 'PRODUCT'), ('Coca-Cola', 28, 37, 'ORG'), ('McDonald', 27, 35, 'ORG'), ('Sayes', 0, 5, 'PERSON'), ('xplatform', 14, 23, 'PERSON'), ('un', 10, 12, 'ORG'), ('Reg', 17, 20, 'PERSON'), ('one', 0, 3, 'CARDINAL'), ('French', 15, 21, 'NORP'), ('Edith', 34, 39, 'PERSON'), (""the People's Republic of"", 15, 39, 'GPE')]",606.4400000000005,"['AI', 'one', '1500']"
North Korea and everything they,6002.32,6008.719,"[('North Korea', 0, 11, 'GPE')]",6.399000000000342,['North Korea']
circus,6089.08,6093.719,"[('circus', 0, 6, 'ORG')]",4.639000000000124,['circus']
algorithm J Transformers uh American politics and elections what 2024 us elections well our goal is to be possible and now in the past Twitter has not been um because Twitter was Donald Trump will come back to the platform he recently posted on Truth every time like 100% it like like it's single thing is a truth like 100% yeah that seems unlikely I think gerle will a big part of Truth so truth social yeah,6103.28,6243.199,"[('J Transformers', 10, 24, 'PRODUCT'), ('American', 0, 8, 'NORP'), ('2024', 0, 4, 'CARDINAL'), ('Twitter', 29, 36, 'ORG'), ('Twitter', 20, 27, 'ORG'), ('Donald Trump', 0, 12, 'PERSON'), ('Truth', 31, 36, 'ORG'), ('100%', 16, 20, 'PERCENT'), ('100%', 29, 33, 'PERCENT'), ('gerle', 28, 33, 'PERSON'), ('Truth', 14, 19, 'ORG')]",139.91899999999987,"['Twitter', 'Truth', '100%']"
think I think uh Donald Trump I think he owns a a big part of Truth social so um platform Community notes might be really than a few hours how do you explain why challenge Wikipedia which Wikipedia is a,6246.8,6391.639,"[('Donald Trump', 17, 29, 'PERSON'), ('Truth', 21, 26, 'ORG'), ('Community', 9, 18, 'ORG'), ('a few hours', 5, 16, 'TIME'), ('Wikipedia', 10, 19, 'ORG'), ('Wikipedia', 26, 35, 'ORG')]",144.83899999999994,"['Wikipedia', 'Donald Trump', 'Truth']"
well Wikipedia is very hierarchical uh,6393.8,6399.599,"[('Wikipedia', 5, 14, 'ORG')]",5.798999999999978,['Wikipedia']
100% all the data is open source 100% so what has Elon Musk been wrong about I really nice uh Elon Musk the man who has,6417.92,6460.56,"[('100%', 0, 4, 'PERCENT'), ('100%', 33, 37, 'PERCENT'), ('Elon Musk', 9, 18, 'PERSON'), ('Elon Musk', 15, 24, 'PERSON')]",42.64000000000033,"['100%', 'Elon Musk']"
cool oh sure I mean uh what do Elon Musk been Elon Musk been wrong about well where do I quite a few blunters in his time and I'm at the Tesla cyber Rodeo uh first off,6468.36,6487.638999999999,"[('Elon Musk', 31, 40, 'PERSON'), ('Elon', 5, 9, 'ORG'), ('Musk', 0, 4, 'PERSON'), ('a few blunters', 6, 20, 'MONEY'), ('Tesla', 7, 12, 'ORG'), ('first', 28, 33, 'ORDINAL')]",19.27899999999954,"['Elon Musk', 'Elon', 'Musk']"
first part uh I did actually have the trial in San Francisco big Civil Trial unanimous Bing of a San Francisco jury um I agreed to to the fine for the SEC was not because the SEC was correct behavior by the SEC corruption frankly to pay pay the fine um Tesla would have,6504.239,6549.0,"[('first', 0, 5, 'ORDINAL'), ('San Francisco', 9, 22, 'GPE'), ('Bing', 10, 14, 'PERSON'), ('San Francisco', 20, 33, 'GPE'), ('SEC', 35, 38, 'ORG'), ('SEC', 20, 23, 'ORG'), ('SEC', 16, 19, 'ORG'), ('Tesla', 23, 28, 'ORG')]",44.76100000000042,"['SEC', 'San Francisco', 'first']"
saying pay $20 million and and and admit told I mean sec in its best form could not once that the SEC go after any of shorting and distorting Tesla investors not once literally a thousand times not once did the SEC pursue because the the the lawyers of the SEC from from the SEC that they're looking told Tesla would would be bankrupt so if if there if there was an SEC investigation like this Banks would immediately at the time MH now we're in a there's a time where Elon called the British cave diver a quote pedo guy in a tii cave that little alur earned cases both both the the the the SEC on the SEC guys lost unanimous jury verdict in San Francisco they picked San Francisco because they thought it was the LA trial was also they picked the about you Elon Musk that's like one of jury Sho for the trying to find the end uh except with Lilith no we'll there uh over the past year or so since necessarily sort of one candidate or for Democrats again no I I would say probably you know half the country is little bit more fun and Good Vibes and Vibes camaraderie humor you know like uh I can only see one side of it so it it one not even no one I'm going to need an at first um okay I forget the rest of six seconds all the seconds there's so much math in Diablo that breaks my brain and neural Nets don't feel pain your for what wor I guess karma be good to  um well the X platform is very um you know I my feeling is that one xplatform to be less negative than the Legacy Media you know I mean if if if xplatform I I mean I really get more one overlapping with like Good Vibes and happen on Earth today mhm and it's a big Lion of there or there's some other so our old friend Tesla autopilot it's probably one of the most intelligent real world AI systems in the world right became more than a robot on four wheels images it's you've agreed with ilas recently where he talked about llm controls out neur all Nets are able to Tesla autopal is doing is it to you,6568.76,7567.719,"[('$20 million', 11, 22, 'MONEY'), ('sec', 12, 15, 'ORG'), ('SEC', 18, 21, 'ORG'), ('Tesla', 24, 29, 'ORG'), ('a thousand', 29, 39, 'CARDINAL'), ('SEC', 23, 26, 'ORG'), ('SEC', 35, 38, 'ORG'), ('SEC', 14, 17, 'ORG'), ('Tesla', 5, 10, 'ORG'), ('SEC', 31, 34, 'ORG'), ('Banks', 24, 29, 'PERSON'), ('MH', 24, 26, 'ORG'), ('Elon', 23, 27, 'ORG'), ('British', 0, 7, 'NORP'), ('alur', 26, 30, 'NORP'), ('SEC', 32, 35, 'ORG'), ('SEC', 7, 10, 'ORG'), ('San Francisco', 11, 24, 'GPE'), ('Francisco', 0, 9, 'GPE'), ('LA', 4, 6, 'GPE'), ('Elon Musk', 10, 19, 'PERSON'), ('Sho', 5, 8, 'PERSON'), ('Lilith', 19, 25, 'PERSON'), ('the past year', 14, 27, 'DATE'), ('one', 20, 23, 'CARDINAL'), ('Democrats', 4, 13, 'NORP'), ('half', 18, 22, 'CARDINAL'), ('Good Vibes', 24, 34, 'PERSON'), ('Vibes', 0, 5, 'ORG'), ('one', 15, 18, 'CARDINAL'), ('one', 0, 3, 'CARDINAL'), ('first', 3, 8, 'ORDINAL'), ('six seconds', 0, 11, 'TIME'), ('all the seconds', 12, 27, 'TIME'), ('Diablo', 13, 19, 'ORG'), ('Nets', 11, 15, 'ORG'), ('wor', 9, 12, 'PERSON'), ('X', 13, 14, 'PRODUCT'), ('one', 33, 36, 'CARDINAL'), ('xplatform', 0, 9, 'PERSON'), ('Legacy Media', 0, 12, 'ORG'), ('xplatform', 0, 9, 'PERSON'), ('one', 0, 3, 'CARDINAL'), ('Good Vibes', 22, 32, 'PERSON'), ('Earth', 10, 15, 'LOC'), ('today', 16, 21, 'DATE'), ('Lion of', 0, 7, 'ORG'), ('Tesla', 18, 23, 'ORG'), ('one', 9, 12, 'CARDINAL'), ('AI', 11, 13, 'PRODUCT'), ('four', 28, 32, 'CARDINAL'), ('ilas', 31, 35, 'GPE'), ('llm', 31, 34, 'PERSON'), ('Nets', 22, 26, 'ORG'), ('Tesla', 0, 5, 'ORG')]",998.9589999999998,"['SEC', 'one', 'Tesla']"
know we only have 100 Watts um and an in 8,7591.28,7601.92,"[('100', 18, 21, 'CARDINAL'), ('8', 13, 14, 'CARDINAL')]",10.640000000000327,"['100', '8']"
computer 144 trillion operations per second which sounds like a lot but is itage it's only 256 understand the world but I think Tesla's about 10 watts of higher brain function that 10 those 10 watts can still produce a much better novel than a 10 megawatt GPU cluster so there's a six order of there um I mean the the AI is thus far gotten to where it is via Brute Force technology you first try to make it work power um Tesla is arguably ahead of the,7598.32,7721.84,"[('144 trillion', 9, 21, 'CARDINAL'), ('second', 0, 6, 'ORDINAL'), ('only 256', 11, 19, 'CARDINAL'), ('Tesla', 33, 38, 'ORG'), ('about 10 watts', 0, 14, 'QUANTITY'), ('10', 5, 7, 'CARDINAL'), ('10 megawatt', 27, 38, 'QUANTITY'), ('six', 25, 28, 'CARDINAL'), ('AI', 24, 26, 'PRODUCT'), ('Brute Force', 26, 37, 'ORG'), ('first', 15, 20, 'ORDINAL'), ('Tesla', 9, 14, 'ORG')]",123.52000000000044,"['Tesla', '144 trillion', 'second']"
to try to understand the world with 100,7723.679,7728.92,"[('100', 36, 39, 'CARDINAL')]",5.2409999999999854,['100']
Watts those with Hardware 4 and then Hardware 5 will be even better better than a human even with Hardware 3 and 100 wat of be probably less than 50 wats what have you learned about uh developing Optimus about world AI into the space of robotic,7727.719,7781.559,"[('Watts', 0, 5, 'ORG'), ('Hardware 4', 11, 21, 'ORG'), ('Hardware', 31, 39, 'ORG'), ('5', 0, 1, 'CARDINAL'), ('3', 39, 40, 'CARDINAL'), ('100', 4, 7, 'CARDINAL'), ('less than 50', 12, 24, 'CARDINAL'), ('wats', 0, 4, 'NORP'), ('Optimus', 20, 27, 'ORG'), ('AI', 6, 8, 'PRODUCT')]",53.840000000000146,"['Watts', 'Hardware 4', 'Hardware']"
shelf Motors like tens of thousands hundreds of thousands of electric motor Boston Dynamics Atlas it's a very make Optimus for less than the cost of a car it should be CU if you look at with fingers so Optimus has really nice touch robotics I mean one of the tests I out um the the car is robot and four wheeels the the the Optimus is a robot ire Machinery of the learning process do Walter isacson in his new biog graphy people it seems like you don't Harbor on to grudges MH does yes I mean one of the things with with too well Elon I just want to say thank friendship over the years for seeing ass off to make it happen thank you Yan thanks Lex thank you for listening to this conversation with Elon Musk to that Walter isacson wrote about the,7793.88,8186.839999999999,"[('Motors', 6, 12, 'ORG'), ('tens of thousands hundreds', 5, 31, 'CARDINAL'), ('thousands', 0, 9, 'CARDINAL'), ('Boston Dynamics Atlas', 0, 21, 'ORG'), ('Optimus', 5, 12, 'ORG'), ('CU', 17, 19, 'ORG'), ('Optimus', 16, 23, 'ORG'), ('one', 22, 25, 'CARDINAL'), ('four', 32, 36, 'CARDINAL'), ('wheeels', 0, 7, 'ORG'), ('Optimus', 20, 27, 'ORG'), ('Machinery of', 4, 16, 'ORG'), ('Walter isacson', 3, 17, 'PERSON'), ('Harbor', 31, 37, 'FAC'), ('MH', 14, 16, 'ORG'), ('one', 11, 14, 'CARDINAL'), ('Elon', 9, 13, 'ORG'), ('the years', 16, 25, 'DATE'), ('Yan', 36, 39, 'PERSON'), ('Lex', 7, 10, 'PERSON'), ('Elon Musk', 23, 32, 'PERSON'), ('Walter isacson', 5, 19, 'PERSON')]",392.9599999999991,"['Optimus', 'one', 'Walter isacson']"
central philosophy of how Elon,8184.559,8189.8,"[('Elon', 26, 30, 'PERSON')]",5.2409999999999854,['Elon']
